EDWIN AU

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER | WEB DESIGNER

https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing

www.linkedin.com/in/eaudesign



416-880-3791



edwinau@rogers.com



PROFILE I'm a full-stack web developer but wear multiple hats with a background in product design and graphic design. I'm passionate about modern and intuitive websites that put user experiences first. I have a Mickey Disney T-shirt Design currently sold at Uniqlo! Feel free to contact me if you're interested to find out how my skills can benefit your team.

EDUCATION



✓ Bitmaker

Web Development Immersive

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

- > Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp
- > Complex object oriented programming
 - > JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, AJAX, PostGres



Ryerson University

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

Sep 1998 - April 2002

> Skills in graphic design, marketing, merchandising and Accounting

> Product Design: 2D vs 3D

> Green Design: Triple Bottom Line

Central Saint Martins (UK)

Experimentation Design Course

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

- > Selected by Ryerson University to partake in this foreign exchange program
- > Complex graphic design tasks
- > Thesis: Vivienne Westwood on Punk

SKILLS























WORK EXPERIENCE

■ RendezYou

Front End Developer, Web Designer @ Mar 2017 - Present https://rendezyou.herokuapp.com

- > Working as Front End Developer and Web Designer for RendezYou, a web app that neatly tucks itself in the online travel and tourism sector.
- > Built with Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, PostGres, Google Maps.
- > Fully responsive for desktops, tablets and mobile devices.

Disney Consumer Products

Product Developer ② Nov 2013 - Apr 2016

www.dcpi.disney.com

- > Provided creative leadership in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Canada.
- > As one of five designers working out of Disney Canada's head office, I guided 50+ licensees with product design ranging from apparel and home accessories, to toys and arts & crafts. These products were widely sold at Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Dollarama, Canadian Tire, just to name a few.
- > I used Photoshop & Illustrator everyday, as well as an online product management software called OPA which allows me to lead licensees through the entire product development cycle.
- > My regular work day can range from approving product designs online, to traveling and meeting with vendors communicating Disney design goals, initiatives and milestones.

Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy)

Associate, Graphic Designer ② Sep 2012 - Sep 2013

- > Having accumulated 10 years of product development experience in Toronto -I've decided to take my skills as a Technical Designer, Fashion Designer, and Product Developer abroad, ending up with the opportunity to work at Dolce & Gabbana's head quarters in Italy Milan for a year, helping their design and sales team with preparation and sales of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections.
- > Achievements: Creating the Fall 2013 sales deck (external) and Spring 2014 employee training material (internal) for the Italian Luxury fashion house. For more information please visit www.edwinau.portfoliobox.net
- > This in-house experience allowed me to see design through a European lens, My daily tasks include utilizing my design skills, photoshop skills, and provide light market analysis to the design/sales team.